I THINK THAT'S WHAT I'M GOING
TO DO.
STEPHEN, CLEARLY YOUR FOCUS ARE
THE TAMALA VENDORS.
THAT'S CLEARLY WHAT YOU ALL ARE
TRYING TO GET AT.
WELL, FIRST OF ALL, HE USES
THE TERM, THINK ABOUT THIS, HE
USES THE TERM INVASION FORCE.
THIS FOOL, GOVERNOR PRISKER,
USES THE TERM INVASION FORCE TO
DESCRIBE FEDERAL LAW ENFORCEMENT.
HE IS ADOPTING THE LANGUAGE AND
THE NARRATIVE OF THE PAID
INSURRECTIONISTS AND THE ANTIFA
MOBS.
THAT'S WHAT I'M GOING TO DO.
THAT'S WHAT BIDEN FLOODED INTO
THIS COUNTRY.
TAKING OUR JOBS, TAKING OUR WAGES,
FILLING UP OUR HOSPITALS,
DESTROYING GOD KNOWS HOW MANY
SCHOOLS AND OF COURSE LEADING
TO COUNTLESS RAPES, ASSAULTS,
AND MURDERS.
THAT WAS THE INVASION FORCE.
PRESIDENT TRUMP WAS ELECTED ON A
MANDATE TO TURN THAT INVASION
BACK TO SEND THOSE ILLEGALS
HOME.
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS REPEATING AND
ATTACKING ICE OFFICERS.
AND HIS LATEST ACT DECLARING
THERE ARE NO-GO ZONES WHERE
FEDERAL LAW ENFORCEMENT IS NOT
PERMITTED IS TRULY AN ACT OF
INSURRECTION AGAINST THE FEDERAL
GOVERNMENT.
DO YOU ANTICIPATE THE FEDERAL
GOVERNMENT WILL CITE THE INSURRECTION
ACT IN ORDER TO RAMP UP FEDERAL
PRESENCE AND FEDERAL PRESENCE
KEPT SAFELY IN A CITY LIKE
CHICAGO?